Fradipta Alqaiyum

Jakarta, Indonesia (+62) 81268-7868-43 fradipta.alqaiyum@gmail.com

Mobile Application Developer with around 3 years experience in software development lifecycle (SDLC) including analysis, design, development, and testing, deployment and documentation as per ISO standards. Experience in Mobile Application Operating systems like iOS and Android. Skilled, motivated and product-oriented mobile application developer with strong Object Oriented Programming Concepts and design skills Experience in developing android and iOS Apps.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Ideon Lab, Surabaya, ID

Mobile Developer Freelancer

January 2019–Present

- Freelancer project that handle by my self.
- Develop, Design, and deliver mobile app project to client
- Completed more than 10 project since 2019
- Using Flutter, Git, Firebase, Google Cloud, Python projects.
- Using Provider, and BloC State Management

PT. Berbagi Solusi Teknologi

Jakarta, ID

Mobile Developer Intern

July 2020 –September 2020

- Contribute on a startup project to build a crowdfunding apps in the pandemic covid-19 era.
- Develop mobile app front end with Flutter Framework
- Using Flutter, Git, Firebase, and Google Cloud for Location
- Using GetX State Management

Revo Apps (Software House)

Surabaya, ID

Junior Mobile Developer

January 2021–March 2021

- Contribute on a startup project called indohobi.id as a mobile developer
- Handle Feature that called Forum Hobi, a feature inside apps to communicate with other peoples.
- Handle a fix or improvement on another feature
- Work with 5 more people on one projects.
- Using Flutter, Git, Firebase, API
- Using Provider State Management

PT. Minasa Finteknologi Syariah

Jakarta, ID

Junior Mobile Developer

March 2021 -April 2022

- Contribute on a startup project called DDS Digital as a mobile developer
- Handle on a whole apps feature.
- Using Flutter, Git, Firebase, API
- Using GetX State Management

Mobile Developer (Intermediate)

January 2022–Present

- Contribute on a PETRONAS Projects that called AssetData.io
- Handle on a whole apps feature.
- Using Flutter, Git, Firebase, API, Google SDK, Sentry, Papertrail.
- Using BloC State Management

Education

- Graduated with 3.4 GPA
- Bachelor Degree of Computer Engineering
- Sepuluh Nopember Institute of Technology, Surabaya, Indonesia
- Graduate 2021
- Thesis: Automated Deep vein thrombosis Segmentation using UNet Architecture Convolutional Neural Network

SKILLS

- Proficient in Flutter Framework
- Basic Knowledge in Kotlin and Swift
- Proficient using Git version control
- Experience using Firebase and Google Cloud SDK Platform
- Proficient deliver application process at Playstore and Appstore or testflight
- CI/CD using codemagic
- Have knowledge on maintenance application through Firebase Analytics, Sentry, and papertrail.